productionparadise.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy policy

### How we handle any personal data you give us

The information that we collect from you is for one purpose only, to improve your experience and help you get the most of ProductionParadise.com and using our platform in a business to business way with your peers. To give you even more peace of mind, we look after your data in the right way and never share it with any 3rd parties.

### What data do we collect?

Subscribers: When you subscribe to our magazines, we request the data below. This list includes some mandatory data which we request from you, in addition to optional data to be sure that we send the most relevant news according to your location and business sector.

  * Name and/or company name
  * Email address
  * Country
  * City
  * Business sector
  * Job title
  * Phone number
  * Website or portfolio link, if you have one

Members: When you become a member of Production Paradise, we request the data below. This list includes some mandatory data which we request from you, in addition to optional data, for the promotion of your services and for accounting purposes.

  * Name and/or company name
  * Email address
  * Country
  * City
  * Business sector
  * Job title
  * Phone number
  * Website or portfolio link, if you have one
  * TAX number
  * Billing address
  * Social media links
  * Your portfolio (this may include images and videos)
  * Text describing your services/bio

### Which providers do we share your data with?

Companies we use to connect with to provide services through our website. For example, we connect with Facebook so you can share our magazines with your Facebook friends and followers. Click on the individual company names to view their privacy policies.

Analytics - GTM with [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)
    Cookies and usage data
Marketing - [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) and [Twitter](https://business.twitter.com/en/help/ads-policies/other-policy-requirements/policies-for-conversion-tracking-and-tailored-audiences.html) pixels
    Cookies and usage data
Advertising - [Google DFP](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
    Cookies and usage data
Handling payments – Redsys
    Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Managing contacts and sending messages - [Sendy](https://sendy.co/privacy-policy), [SES](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/), [Salesmanago](https://www.salesmanago.com/info/gdpr.htm)
    Name and/or company name, email address, country, city, business sector, job title, phone number, website or portfolio link, usage data
SPAM protection - [Akismet](https://akismet.com/tos/) and [Google reCAPTCHA](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
    Various types of data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Interaction with external social networks and platforms - [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) Like button and social widgets, [Pinterest](https://policy.pinterest.com/privacy-policy) and [Google +1](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
    Cookies and usage data
Content performance and features testing (A/B testing) - [Google optimize](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
    Cookies and usage data

### Which 3rd parties do we share your data with?

We do will not share your data with any third parties, unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

### How long do we keep your data?

Your data will be kept as long as you don’t unsubscribe or ask your date to be erased.

### Where is it stored?

All data is stored on our secure European based servers

### Do we have lawful reasons why we need this data?

The lawful reasons why we need this data are legitimate interests pursued by the company, as established by the GDPR (Article 6).

### What do we do with this information?

Analyse user activity to improve our service, Provide a high quality and ultimately useful user experience throughout our site and email communication. We may notify you by email or phone with important information of relevance to you/your company, for example if someone is interested in your services, or with news, updates to our site, promotional offers, tips, etc. 

### IP addresses and Cookies

IP address is stored temporarily for security and spam prevention.

productionparadise.com uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record session information, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customise Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

Cookies are text files that are either temporarily stored in the random access memory or on the hard drive of your computer. They generally serve for offering you the services of productionparadise.com within your personal settings of each new session, which basically means to give you a better and faster experience more in tune with what you like to see. Cookies are partly stored permanently on your hard drive. You may prevent this by setting your browser accordingly, however you may notice that our website does not run as fast and in the same way to what you would expect.

### Technical security

We will report any data breaches and security issues to the data protection authority within 72 hours of discovery. We will also notify by email any users who are directly affected by this breach.

### How you can control the use and display of your information?

All data that we gather is used to give you the best possible experience on our website.

  * You have the right to request to edit or erase certain information about you, but this may result in our site being less useful for you.
  * You have the right for your information about you to be erased from our site. You can do that by sending an email to [privacy@productionparadise.com](mailto:privacy@productionparadise.com).
  * If you want to opt-out of the emails we send you, you will find an “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of every newsletter you get from us. To opt-in send us an email to [privacy@productionparadise.com](mailto:privacy@productionparadise.com) requesting to receive our newsletters. Certain important emails may still be sent to you, for example about invoices (for members).
  * You can request to see details of any personal information which we hold about you. If you would like to see this information, please contact us at: [privacy@productionparadise.com](mailto:privacy@productionparadise.com). You will need to provide proof of your identity and we may charge a fee to provide this information. Requests of information will take up to 30 days.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. This page will show a notice that changes have been made. If a user objects to the updated Privacy Policy, they should request for their account to be erased and personal data removed.

We hope that this Privacy Policy answers any questions that you may have. If you have any further questions, feel free to contact us directly here by email at: [privacy@productionparadise.com](mailto:privacy@productionparadise.com)

### Contact us

Production Media Network  
Moll de Barcelona s/n, World Trade Center  
Edif. Nord, Planta 3  
08039 Barcelona (Spain)  
V.A.T. NUMBER: ESB63519847  
Company Registration Number: 08150063268  
Email: [privacy@productionparadise.com](mailto:privacy@productionparadise.com)
